// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
let questions = [{
  numb: 1,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Greece?",
  answer: "Athens",
  options: ["Thessaloniki", "Larissa", "Athens", "Patra"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of England?",
  answer: "London",
  options: ["Manchester", "London", "Birmingham", "Liverpool"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Italy?",
  answer: "Rome",
  options: ["Milan", "Naples", "Turin", "Rome"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of France?",
  answer: "Paris",
  options: ["Paris", "Marseille", "Lyon", "Toulouse"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Spain?",
  answer: "Madrid",
  options: ["Barcelona", "Valencia", "Madrid", "Sevilla"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Germany?",
  answer: "Berlin",
  options: ["Munich", "Berlin", "Hamburg", "Frankfurt"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Portugal?",
  answer: "Lisbon",
  options: ["Porto", "Braga", "Coimbra", "Lisbon"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Scotland?",
  answer: "Edinburgh",
  options: ["Edinburgh", "Glasgow", "Aberdeen", "Dundee"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Switzerland?",
  answer: "Bern",
  options: ["Zurich", "Geneva", "Basel", "Bern"]
},

// The code has been taken by https://www.codingnepalweb.com/ and i have adjusted it in my needs
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which of the below is the capital of Austria?",
  answer: "Vienna",
  options: ["Salzburg", "Vienna", "Graz", "Linz"]
},
];